Hurry, hurry!
Quick, take a look.
Dad, how is it, Dad?
Tianting,
why are you being so mischievous?
Why did you reach your hand down?
I grabbed the wrong hand.
I didn't reach my hand down.
Quick, go get a knife!
I'm going to chop this hand off.
Master.
He can still walk with two extra hands.
It's better than having broken legs.
Exactly.
It's just...
buying shoes won't be easy.
You...
Hurry up and go!
Chief Leng.
You followed the scent here.
Where is the stuff I asked for?
I've had it ready for you.
Take a look.
I even gave you extra.
Doing business with me...
...guarantees you a profit.
You kept your word.
I'm off.
Chief Leng.
I have another job for you.
Are you interested?
You already have the Curse Scripture and the Celestial Seal.
What more do you want?
Look into someone for me.
Li Xiao.
He also wants the position of Chief.
A warlord's son like him...
...wants to find the Tidal Tomb from twenty years ago?
Even if he has a strong army...
...and a fate as tough as yours,
...without the guidance of the Dragon-Seeking Lineage,
...he wouldn't even know where the tomb's entrance is.
Exactly.
If he becomes Chief...
...it probably isn't to raid tombs and suppress evil.
I think...
...he wants to swallow up The Four Great Families.
That's why...
...I want your help to find the Qi family's Talisman Book ASAP.
And the Wan family's Yin-Yang Eyes.
I absolutely can't let him become the Chief before me.
Help you?
But I've already gotten what I wanted.
What else can you offer me?
There must be something else you want.
Why don't you think about it?
My corpse poison isn't completely cleared.
You'll continue to clear the poison for me.
Come here.
I...
Last time I cleared it for you...
Young Master, bad news!
It's not what you think.
I was just clearing her poison.
What is it? Spit it out.
A guy named Li Xiao has our house surrounded with his men!
He says he's here to catch an adulterer.
He showed up at our door this fast?
Catch an adulterer?
I'm not getting involved in this.
Jiushuang,
this marriage was arranged by our families.
With this behavior of yours,
how does that make the Li family look?
So the Li family's reputation matters,
but my life doesn't?
Wait.
Did these despicable people from the Sheng family
put a spell on you?
The Sheng family treats guests well,
but it depends on who they are.
I was wondering who it was.
Turns out it's a prodigy who mooches off two families.
Young Master Li.
You can't force love.
It just needs to quench my thirst.
Jiushuang,
why do you insist on being with him?
Well...
Because I'm the one she loves.
You...
Is that so hard to understand?
Rat,
do you understand?
Of course I do.
Even a pig could.
I...
I don't get it.
If I don't teach you all a lesson,
you'll really think I'm here to joke around.
Head of the Sheng family, right?
Let me tell you,
to me, you're all less than ants.
Jiushuang,
come back with me.
Li Xiao, right?
Marrying Miss Mei is just a front.
You're actually after this, aren't you?
The Celestial Seal.
Look. It really is for the Celestial Seal.
Mei Jiushuang,
you actually gave the Mei family's greatest treasure to an outsider?
Compared to a two-faced person like you,
he's much more worthy of my trust.
Fine, fine, fine.
In that case,
if I can't have it,
no one else will either!
I've always wanted to see if your dark magic is faster,
or my gun!
Zhang Tianyou!
I thought you had some real skills.
That's it?
Jiushuang,
now you can come back with me.
It seems
you still don't have what it takes.
You don't deserve this thing at all.
I'll keep it safe for you.
Apologize properly to Miss Mei,
and stop coveting any family of Wan Mei Qi Sheng.
You're not worthy.
Retreat! Retreat!
If I may say so, Young Master,
we're just letting them go?
What use do I have keeping an idiot like him?
Wait, let me see.
Where's your bullet hole?
Hey, don't, don't, don't!
What's going on?
What's this inside?
The Dragon Scale Armor.
How do you have the legendary Dragon Scale Armor?
This, this...
Never mind about that.
Anyway, I did what I promised you.
Zhang Tianyou!
Did I, your first wife,
interrupt your good time?
Zhang Tianyou, you bastard!
He ruined your brother's legs,
and I haven't even settled the score with him yet.
He actually used a fake Curse Scripture
to swindle my tiny plot of land!
Doesn't he like land?
I'll give him a graveyard!
Understood, Father.
I guarantee he'll rest in peace.
Zhang Tianyou is the live-in son-in-law of my Sheng family.
Even as a ghost, he still is.
Now get out!
Miss Sheng's temper
is about to burn the house down.
I'm used to it.
Zhang Tianyou,
those two damaged Puppet Corpses
were fed my Mei family's Five Venomous Creatures,
which is how the Celestial Seal
and my special spices controlled them.
They used to be living people, too.
Understood.
Rat,
pack up.
We act after dark.
Got it.
Young Master.
A kind-hearted person like Miss Mei
is rare to find in our line of work.
A kind heart is a good thing,
but it can easily cause trouble sometimes.
Zhang Tianyou,
how do you know about our Mei family's Celestial Seal?
And where did you get the Dragon Scale Armor?
Let me tell you, Miss Mei.
Our Young Master knows more than just the Celestial Seal.
He also knows about the Talisman Book,
and the Curse Scripture.
I mean,
he's no ordinary man.
Our Young Master...
Well, our Young Master...
It's a Sealed Door!
A Sealed Door!
Someone wants to trap us in here like dumpling filling.